I promised
myself I wasn't going to do that in this series
but I'll have to appeal
day 12
things aren't happening the way I want them to
and we're going to accept that,
right bro
otherwise we get a lot ah
it seems that i get asked someone to mention my purchase
my Passenger
that i am an interesting person
we have to start taking care
for our resilience
don't become stupid
knows face
if i'm not being interesting to girls
to their point
can't find my time roll
i have to be attractive enough to be noticed
is on
the problems not so with them
the problem is with me
man let's take responsibility
and fix it from now on
it's fire in the playground man
either go or crack
in this series I don't even have one
if the guys aren't noticing their work
be irresistible
I have an idea and I'm going to invest in it again
now i need to do something creative
different
impact
so I can give 1 bang soon
there are only a few days left
so my money is running out
and I need to do something
so let's go to this
it went to the store and has no
it's bro to vary what I want doesn't have
have to walk there for about two hundred meters
correria nor uncle
real life you're on
where bro
thank you brother
go save me hand
worth Cara
good people
miner is too good a people it's on
and then it's good that
that you have there
pot cake
1 more time
т о а а аи